They've broken through the front lines!
I've lost contact with the capital!
There's too many of them!
Stand fast!
Finish them!
Where's B-127?
Sorry I'm late. I hit a little traffic.
Get down! Incoming!
Optimus.
Decepticons, attack!
Autobots, fall back! Get to the tower!
Destroy the launch pad!
Let none escape!
Cybertron has fallen.
Get to the escape pods.
There are other Autobots
scattered across the galaxy.
We must reach them if we hope to survive.
Optimus, this is our home.
We have to fight for it.
We will fight on.
But we must find refuge first.
I found a planet
that's well hidden. Earth.
You will travel there
and establish a base for us.
Once we've gathered the others,
we'll join you.
You must protect the planet.
If the Decepticons find it,
then our people are truly finished.
Now go!
Good luck, soldier.
I'll buy you some time.
No!
Okay, okay!
I'm dead already, man!
Not just you.
Being the overachiever that you are,
you managed to get
your whole squad killed, Danny.
Bravo.
- Come on, man. Those things sting.
- What things? These things?
You know, I wouldn't know.
I haven't been hit yet.
Okay, you know what?
That's too close, man.
You could've taken out an eye.
I got a date tonight, man.
This ain't sexy!
You're right. I'm sorry.
That one was on me.
That's a malfunctioning trigger.
This weapon is just faulty.
Someone is going to get a talking to...
Man, would you stop?
All right, just stop.
I should've let you die in Grenada.
If you did, we wouldn't be able
to come to the forest,
run around and play these awesome games.
Exactly.
I hate you.
Wow, man, that hurts. 'Cause I love you.
But you refuse to let it in
'cause you got intimacy issues.
A therapist will probably tell you
you weren't hugged enough as a kid.
- Look, man.
- Danny, I know I look stupid, but...
Hey, yo, take cover!
Danny.
You okay?
Yeah, man.
This is Agent Jack Burns.
I need medical up here now.
We have a projectile strike
in the northwest corner
of the training course.
Multiple injuries.
And would someone please explain to me
why you dropped napalm on your own guys!
Negative. There are no live fire drills
in the northwest sector.
What the hell hit us, then?
Target on your right!
I need all of you to fan out
and track that thing down now!
Drive!
There!
What the hell?
Take it down!
Get down there now
and flush that thing out!
There it is!
Target has been located, sir.
Light it up!
Damn it!
Oh, no.
It's going for the mine! Cut it off!
Move, move!
Please.
This is a mistake.
Stay cool. Hold your fire.
I don't want to hurt anyone.
Who called in the Air Force?
That's not the Air Force.
Run.
Did you think you could hide?
Now you'll die screaming.
Like your friends!
Tell me where your friends are hiding.
I'll never talk.
Is that right?
Then let's make it official.
B-127...
As a member
of the Autobot resistance,
you are a traitor to Cybertron
and are hereby sentenced
to death.
No!
Shut up.
♪ Sweetness, sweetness
I was onlyjoking
♪ When I said by rights
You should be
♪ Bludgeoned in your bed
♪ And now I know
how Joan of Arc felt
♪ Now I know
Morning, Dad.
♪ As the flames rose
To her Roman nose
♪ And her Walkman
Started to melt
♪ Bigmouth, la-da-da da-da
♪ Bigmouth...
No! Don't tickle.
Caught.
Gross, Ron.
Excuse me.
Are those your diving trophies?
Taking up too much space in my room.
You're gonna regret doing that.
Where's breakfast?
Breakfast is conveniently located
in the cupboards and the fridge.
Try to help out...
- Yeah.
- ...a little.
Since I'm such a big kid now,
making my own breakfast and what have you,
you know how I could be
an even bigger help around here, Mom?
If I had a car.
Charlie.
What do you know,
it's my birthday tomorrow,
perfect timing for a large cash gift.
You know, $500 is really all I need
to finish the Corvette.
I don't have $500.
You know how much nurses make.
"Half as much as doctors
for twice the work," right?
Tell you what, kiddo...
I got another job interview tomorrow.
If all goes well,
I'll have you swimming in car parts.
I prefer cash, Ron.
Don't be rude. Feed the dog.
Conan is Otis's dog. Make him do it.
What?
You look so grown up in your karate suit.
My baby boy is becoming a man.
Shoot, I'm gonna be late.
Can you drop your brother at karate
on your way to work, please?
I could if I had a car.
Just let him follow you on your bike
so nobody abducts him.
Abducts him?
You just said he's a grown man now.
If anyone tries anything,
I will rupture their freaking spleen.
♪ And do you feel scared?
I do
♪ But I won't stop and falter
♪ And if we threw it all away
♪ Things can only
get better...
- That's two for you guys.
- Thanks, bro.
All right. Have a good one.
Eat safe.
Excuse me. Hi. We've never actually met...
Sorry, I can't right now.
Yeah. Oh, okay.
Hey, hot dog girl!
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry. Oh, God.
Someone's getting fired.
If I had to wear that,
I would pray to be fired.
Good one, Tina.
Let's go.
♪ On the street where you live
♪ Girls talk about their social lives
♪ They're made of lipstick
Plastic and paint
♪ A touch of sable in their eyes
♪ All your life
All you asked
♪ When is your Daddy
Gonna talk to you
♪ But we're living
In another world
♪ Tryin' to get
Your message through...
Come on.
Hey, Uncle Hank.
Are you still working on that damn car?
You still working
on that damn personality?
- What have you got for me?
- Whatever you want.
Russians are gonna
blow us all to hell anyway.
That's the spirit.
Hey, kid.
Hand me the three-eighths, would you?
You working on the carburetor?
- You need the half-inch.
- I said the three...
- Thanks, kid.
- Yep.
♪ You saw me standing
♪ By the wall corner
Of a main street
♪ Take a chance
♪ Like all dreamers
Can't find another way
♪ You don't have
To dream it all
♪ Just live a day...
♪ Don't save a prayer for me now
Where is Optimus Prime?
He survived the fall of Cybertron.
And no rebellion is truly dead
until the leader is vanquished.
So where is he?
My name is Cliffjumper,
lieutenant in the Autobot resistance.
My safe return will be considered...
Wrong answer.
We know he's planning to establish a base.
Tell us where it is
and we'll let you live.
My name is Cliffjumper, lieutenant...
♪ Sometimes you want to go...
No.
That's B-127's signal.
- Can you trace it?
- Already did.
If you won't tell us where Prime is,
perhaps your young friend will.
Never.
You're a brave warrior.
You deserve a better death.
But then again...
Set course for Earth.
I'll give you thirty bucks for all of it.
I can get twice that much
for the coil alone.
From who?
I'm the only one that comes in here.
I don't even know how you're still open.
Just take it. Go. My show is on.
Hey, where did you get that Beetle?
I swear to God, ever since
they put up that dumbass tower,
I can't get a signal to watch my shows.
I've got to see what happens
to Alf this week.
Come on!
Are you kidding me?
Damn it.
I give up.
I can't do this without you.
Nice to meet you.
Interested in a new Buick?
- Nice try.
- All right, I touched. But I didn't eat.
And I'm supposed to believe
one of these steaks
just got up and walked away on its own?
I've seen stranger.
No dinner for you tonight.
But I'm starved!
I've been fasting since lunch!
Well, I did eat that pumpkin.
Happy birthday.
I miss you, Dad.
I think it's too low, honey.
No. No, I think it goes to that button.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. I don't know about... Fix it.
Hey.
- Good morning, birthday girl!
- Hi.
You look...
Nice.
Happy birthday, baby.
I love you. Come on, open your present.
I'm gonna be late for work.
Thanks, Mom.
Helmet. With...
Daffodils.
So, I keep hearing
about people on mopeds getting
run over and their brains smashed in.
You got to wear this from now on.
I don't care if it's not the law.
It's our law.
Plus, look how cute it is.
Yeah.
Happy birthday.
I actually got you
a little gift, too, Charlie.
I mean, it's small,
but, it's from the heart.
A smile is a powerful thing.
It releases endorphins.
It says to the world,
"I'm fun and approachable."
You know, there's a whole chapter in here
about how people who smile more often
actually have more friends.
That's unbelievable.
I really think
it's gonna change your whole outlook
if you smile more often.
I want the Beetle.
- What?
- The yellow Beetle, I want it.
I'll make you a deal.
If I get that thing started, it's mine.
That's no deal.
That's just you taking my car.
If I get it started, I keep it
and I work here every day for a year.
I'll scrub the grease
off the floors, okay?
I will pick up and organize
every scrap of paper in this place.
I'll even detail your horrible,
disgusting toilets.
Please. It's my birthday.
Sorry, no deal.
'Cause we ain't hiring.
It's yours, kid. Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
And my toilets are gorgeous.
♪ Think about it
There must be higher love
♪ Down in the heart or hidden
In the stars above
♪ Without it
Life is a wasted time...
Oh, God, please.
Come on.
Oh, my...
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, thank you so much!
I love you!
- That thing ain't even safe to drive.
- It's a deathtrap.
She's happy, though.
♪ Bring me a higher love
♪ Where's that higher love
I keep thinking of?
Man.
Looks amazing.
What?
Oh, my God.
Charlie, what was that noise?
Nothing! I'm fine. Mom, you should
go back to bed. Everything's fine.
- What the hell is that?
- It's...
What is that car doing in our garage?
Car?
That car
is my car.
Uncle Hank gave it to me.
It runs. Yeah.
Those aren't safe.
I wish you would've told me
before you brought it home.
Okay. Sorry.
- I'm in the middle of some stuff, Mom.
- Okay, I'll get out of your hair, but...
Tell me things sometime.
- I'm your mother.
- Okay.
Okay.
Good night.
- It really runs?
- Yeah, it really runs.
Cool.
You still in there?
Okay.
A little jumpy. I'm sorry.
Hi.
Oh, God, are you...
Do you speak?
I won't hurt you.
Can you understand me?
What are you?
Where did you come from?
Okay. It's okay.
You like my shirt?
You a metal fan?
No, wait...
Oh, who? Me?
Who am I?
I'm...
Charlie.
Charlie Watson.
I'm 18.
Today.
Actually, it's my birthday today.
What's your name?
You don't know
or you don't have a name?
You sound like a little bumblebee.
I'm gonna call you that from now on.
Bumblebee.
Matches your outfit, too.
I want a divorce, Roy!
Come on, Amber.
Give me one good reason.
You tried to sleep with my sister!
Unsuccessfully!
Yeah, you're unsuccessful at everything.
That down payment was for a house.
You bought a car.
How stupid are you, Roy?
We don't need a car. God!
Now, just settle down for one second
and hear me out.
- What the hell is that?
- What?
Oh, God, Roy,
that thing is coming right for us!
No, no, no, no, no...
Not my car. Not my car.
Please, God, no, not my car!
Oh, thank God, my car.
Yeah, I'm okay.
That's good, baby. That's good.
Run. Run!
God!
Is that my car?
Hello...
Jeez!
Earth.
Roy!
How underwhelming.
The indigenous life is even more primitive
than I expected.
Hey...
I like the way they pop.
Focus, comrade.
B-127's distress signal came
from the western coast of this continent.
For now, we head west.
When do they start
letting you use nunchucks?
I don't know, but I hope soon.
- Morning! See you guys later.
- Where you off to so fast?
Nowhere. Have a nice day.
Morning...
Bee?
Bee, where are you?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Bee!
Where did you go?
Otis!
Have you seen my car?
Unfortunately, yes.
No, have you seen my car today?
It was in the garage. Someone stole it!
No, idiot. Mom took it.
She had to bring Conan to the vet
because he swallowed, like,
a rubber glove or something
and Ron needed the station wagon.
Thank God.
Wait.
Hi. Excuse me. It's me again.
- We never officially met, but...
- I can't right now. Sorry.
Nope. Yep.
Okay.
I know, buddy. Hang in there.
You can't eat everything you see.
Just let this be
a good life lesson for you.
Oh, my God. Stop it! Don't do that!
Bee, no!
Mom?
Jesus! Charlie, what are you doing?
Mom, you gotta pull over.
- What the hell is going on?
- Just pull the car over.
Okay, okay. All right.
Would you put that robot junk away?
What are you thinking?
You almost gave me a heart attack.
I thought I was being carjacked.
I'm taking the dog to the vet.
I can't believe you would take him
without me. Mom, I'm so worried about him!
He's my dog, too, you know.
What happened to Conan being Otis's dog?
Mom, you're being hysterical, okay?
You should not be driving
in such an emotional state.
I know how you get during emergencies.
I'm a nurse.
Not of animals.
Okay. I'm happy for you to drive.
You weren't wearing your helmet,
by the way.
- I saw that.
- Oh, shoot.
Keep it together, Bee.
Sir?
Sir.
I thought
you'd want to see this immediately.
- They sure?
- Yes, sir.
Two of them just made contact in Texas.
Intel says they're heading west fast.
Saddle up, Simmons.
We're going to Texas.
Okay, Bee,
we need to go over a few things.
Okay. We're all clear.
All right. I'm re-thinking the beach.
I'm good.
No, I'm good, thanks.
People can be terrible about things
they don't understand.
If they find you, they'll probably
lock you up in a lab somewhere
and cut you into tiny little pieces.
It'll be bad, trust me.
The only person you can show
yourself around is me, okay?
So let's practice. You ready?
If you see anyone besides me,
what do you do?
Great. Perfect. Come back now.
Okay, so let's say we're driving
and all of a sudden...
Oh, shoot! Somebody's here!
Hide, Bee, hide!
You serious?
Bee, it's too late. You're already dead.
It's all right.
That's why we're practicing.
You'll get it.
Fox-2 on approach.
Non-biologicals are inbound.
The goal, sir,
should be to communicate with them.
First contact with an alien species.
I've spent my whole life
waiting for this moment.
If they make one wrong move,
we put 'em down.
The humans are multiplying.
Please let me kill them.
Not yet. B-127's signal has gone silent.
I have an idea.
Listen up! I'm Agent Burns
and this is Dr. Powell.
We currently have 100 guns
pointed right at your head!
So state your business.
People of Earth,
we are Decepticon peacekeepers
patrolling the galaxy.
What are you doing?
This is humiliating.
We believe a dangerous criminal
from our world
is hiding somewhere on yours.
How is it you think we can help?
We need your eyes.
Wait.
You want access to our satellites?
Our scanners' range is limited.
Your infrastructure is primitive.
But combined,
they could be quite powerful.
No way! Out of the question!
We have a common enemy, Agent Burns.
There's a war raging on our planet.
If B-127 isn't found,
that war may find its way here.
Perhaps...
We can find a way to help one another.
We'll talk it over with our superiors.
In the meantime, if you could follow us.
Very well, friend Powell.
Take us to your leader.
Must suck being cooped up
in a VW all day, huh?
Is there anyone that can help you?
Do you have a family?
You know, like a mom, dad, siblings?
You all love each other?
Or drive each other crazy
and you can't wait to get away
and start a whole new life.
Do you want me to see if I can fix it?
I'll be gentle, I promise.
You lay down, okay?
Hold still.
I think maybe there's something...
B-127, I pray this message finds you.
Our war rages on.
...planet Earth...
...survival...
Ravage, eject!
...your mission...
...soldier...
I...
Are you okay?
Who was that?
That voice said something about a war.
Do you remember anything?
Is the VW Beetle some kind of disguise?
Are you hiding from something?
Are you scared?
It's broken.
It's okay.
I think I can help.
Let's go home.
...and a basket case,
a princess...
- And a criminal.
- All right, I'm almost done.
Does that answer your question?
No way. Are you actually watching it?
♪ Don't you forget about me
♪ Don't, don't, don't...
You can pop in another one if you want.
Come on, sweetie!
You got this, Charlie girl!
All right, Charlie girl!
Hello, Brighton Falls.
This is Charlie Watson,
future Olympic gold medalist.
That was so perfect.
- Thanks, Dad.
- How do you feel?
No, no, why would you play this?
Sorry. I just...
I finished.
Let's see if we got something.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, my God, yes!
It worked!
Look at you go.
You got some moves.
You know, Bee, music can help you
say what you're feeling.
You're gonna love this. It's brand new.
♪ Girlfriend in a coma, I know
♪ I know, it's serious
Not a Smiths fan.
Okay.
Here.
Try this.
♪ Never gonna give you up...
Fine.
Okay, where's my Stevie Nicks?
Joan Jett and the Blackhearts.
Stones.
Hey, hey,
please don't touch those. Please.
They belonged to my dad.
Do you want to hear it?
We used to listen to this
while we'd work on the Corvette.
♪ Oh, my love,
My darling...
It was his favorite.
♪ I've hungered for your touch
A long lonely time
He used to say
it would make the car feel better.
♪ Time...
♪ ...goes by so slowly
We used to work on this car
every weekend together.
♪ And time can do so much
It was our thing.
♪ Are you still mine?
That tape...
♪ I need your love
That was the last time I saw him.
He died of a heart attack.
♪ God speed your love to me
I never got to say goodbye.
You know,
I always thought if I could just
finish fixing this car...
♪ Lonely rivers flow to the sea, to the sea
If I could just get it
to start up again,
he would hear me.
He would hear me.
♪ Oh, my love...
I say this with all due respect.
Have you lost your damn mind?
- That was with all due respect?
- The man's got a point, Doctor.
Our satellite network is at the forefront
of our national defense.
Sir, please. It could be
a once in a lifetime opportunity.
Can you imagine the advances an alliance
with these creatures might bring?
I imagine the advances.
An advance on Washington.
- New York. An advance on Chicago!
- That's not gonna happen.
They literally
call themselves "Decepticons."
That doesn't set off any red flags?
Enough! From both of you.
Sir,
we're talking about the most advanced
robotic system ever seen.
If we tell them no,
they'll just take their technology
to the Russians instead.
Do you really want to go down in history
as the man who cost us the Cold War?
Fine.
We'll help them find their fugitive.
And when it's done,
you can do all the experiments you want.
Yes, sir.
Gentle... Robots.
Welcome to Sector 7.
How kind of you to finally allow us in.
We're very happy
to have you here as friends.
Thank you, friend Powell.
My superior has agreed to grant you
limited access to our satellites.
In addition, you're welcome to use
all of our technology here.
It's the largest super-array
of Crays on Earth.
We thank you for your hospitality.
Tell me, those vocal communication
devices you use,
do they function worldwide?
The telephones? Yes, why?
You got to pick a station, man.
I know there's a lot of choices.
"You want to go on a date with me, maybe?"
Okay.
What are you trying to do?
Here we go. Here we go.
You're not a nerd. You're not a nerd.
Okay, you're a nerd, but just
don't let her see that you're nerdy.
Excuse me. Sorry to barge in. I just...
Do you, just...
No, no, it's fine! Just...
Just sit down, please?
Don't scream, okay?
What is that?
It's okay, okay?
Just breathe. Breathe.
- First of all, hi.
- Hi.
I'm Charlie.
I'm Memo, hi.
Hi, Memo.
It's nice to meet you.
Pleasure... Pleasure...
Look, I know what you saw
was a little crazy. I can explain.
Yeah, I can't explain.
But here's the deal.
If you tell anyone what you just saw,
I'm gonna have to
run you over with my car.
Jeez.
That was...
I don't mean that in a mean way. Okay?
What I'm saying
is no one can know
what you just saw, okay?
You promise?
Yeah.
Okay.
Bumblebee, you can come out now.
What?
It's...
He.
He's been going up and down on that dial
all day today and I don't know why.
- Hey, check out his reflexes.
- What?
Oh, God!
Yo, give me your shirt.
Give me your shirt.
You mean the shirt that I'm wearing?
Yes, yes! Come on.
I'll give it back to you.
Okay.
Come on! Give me your shirt!
All right.
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey, no, no! You don't need to do this.
- Yes, I do.
- No, but...
- Come here. Come on!
- No, I get it. I get it!
♪ There's a room
where the light won't find you
Sorry.
I know I promised you, but, yeah,
you're not getting that back.
♪ When they do, I'll be right behind you
♪ So glad we've almost made it
♪ So sad they had to fade it
♪ Everybody wants
to rule the world...
It's incredible!
They're combining
our technology seamlessly.
Satellites, phones, computers.
They're creating an interconnected
web of information.
Volumes of data at their fingertips.
It's revolutionary.
He's a weird guy.
You ever notice that about Powell?
They're tracking fluctuations
in Energon levels.
It's like a heat signature
specific to their species.
It's astonishing.
It's beautiful. It's...
Hello? Hello?
You've given them our satellites,
our comms, God knows what else.
Yet in the space of a day
they've given us a way
to not only hunt down B-127,
but all of them.
Let them finish what they're doing.
Let them find B-127.
And then I'll give you permission
to destroy them all.
Use them for spare parts.
Sir, yes, sir.
So you have no idea where he came from?
No idea.
You thought about calling the cops?
What are they gonna do, Memo?
They're just gonna send him away to a lab
and do weird science experiments on him.
Weird Science!
Plastic tubes and pots and pans...
You're getting pretty good
with that radio dial, Bee.
Yeah, D.J. Bumble in the house!
I can't live without my radio
Is that why
you're always messing with the dial?
You're trying to teach yourself
how to talk, aren't you?
Walk like a man, talk like a man...
No way.
Oh, my God, Bee, you're a genius!
You're an actual genius!
- What is going on here?
- That's Jim from sixth period.
He said he was busy this week.
You want to check it out?
- This is pretty cool.
- Okay.
Bee, we'll be right back.
Don't do anything crazy.
Hey, everybody, come watch!
Tripp's gonna jump!
You're off your nut.
- What's going on over there?
- Don't do it, dude, you're crazy.
Come on, it's not that big a jump.
God, is that Tripp Summers?
You know Tripp?
I mean, yeah. I spilled
a gallon of lemonade on him once.
Doesn't anyone have the balls
to jump off this thing with me?
A brave volunteer.
Yeah, I... See, I didn't...
I didn't do that. I didn't actually...
You got the touch
You got the power
Yeah
Hey, I know you.
No, sorry about that. It...
You were on the dive team
with my little sister.
I saw you win state a couple years ago.
- Yeah.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
This just got
a whole lot more interesting.
We have a championship high-diver
on our hands!
Yeah, I actually, I don't, I don't...
I don't do it anymore.
Don't worry. I won't make you go first.
Watch it!
Yeah, Tripp!
- Yeah!
Dive Girl!
You better not back out on me.
You guys, she's gonna do it!
She's gonna do it!
Dive! Dive! Dive! Dive!
Come on!
You got this, Charlie girl!
- Where you going?
- What, are you scared?
- You okay?
- Let's just go.
What a loser!
Thought you said
you were on the diving team.
I think she's gonna cry in her car.
Where you going, sweetie?
What happened out there?
That was your big moment to look cool.
What's your damage, Tina?
Is that the churro guy?
Where's your hairnet, dude?
It's in the garbage, Einstein.
You throw them away after each use.
For sanitary purposes, obviously, but...
This car is an embarrassment.
You should have your dad
buy you a better one.
Oh, wait...
Sorry.
You okay?
I'm fine.
They're idiots.
But I think I know something
that'll make you feel better.
What?
Revenge.
I don't want revenge.
I do.
What about you, Bee?
Want some revenge?
I just want...
Revenge!
I'm mad
Come on. I got an idea.
This is Tina's house.
And this, it's toilet paper.
You use it for when you...
Here, just take a roll.
No, no, no, no. You've got...
You got to throw it.
Like this.
Not bad.
Not... Yeah...
Okay, look, Bee, you be our egg man.
- Right? Yeah. So...
- Love that.
You see these right here?
You grab one of these, like so.
- And that right there, that's your target.
- That's right.
All right? Just throw it like this.
- I think we could just hand it to him...
- He could maybe, yeah, and then...
- Bee, what are...
- What...
Don't hurt me.
Oh, my God...
Oh, shit!
- Hide, hide, hide.
- Hide!
- Stay...
- Okay!
Okay. Okay.
Hide, Bee!
Go, go, go!
Mom!
That was insane!
My heart right now is going crazy.
- Oh, God.
- Stop the car, please.
Bee, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I can't drive 55!
Bumblebee!
♪ I can't drive 55!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, we're committing a felony!
♪ When I drive that slow, you know
it's hard to steer
We got a yellow vehicle driving
its damn self through the Pico Tunnel.
♪ "We're gonna throw your ass
in the cityjoint"
♪ Looked me in the eye
Said, "You get my point?"
♪ I said yeah! Oh, yeah!
Good night.
Good night, Bee.
Morning, buddy.
I got to go to work, okay?
Bee. Listen to me.
You need to stay in this garage, okay?
After what happened last night, I'm pretty
sure the cops are looking for you,
and you don't exactly blend in.
I'll be back, all right?
Here.
You can have my Pop-Tart.
I need you to go to the
frozen banana stand and steal some sticks.
We're out of sticks.
Can't we just sell the hot dogs
without the sticks?
No.
What's happening here?
We got a hit, I think.
Where's that location?
Near San Francisco.
A coastal town named Brighton Falls.
You have a personal call.
- Hello?
- Charlie, hey, it's Memo.
You got to come home right now.
It's bad. It's really, really bad.
Where's Bumblebee?
Bumblebee, what have you done?
What were you thinking? What...
I told you to hide in the garage!
Great.
Helpful shame spiral, Bee.
I'm not mad, okay? This is all my fault.
I never should have left you.
Hey, okay, maybe don't transform
all the way?
We've still got
to get you through the door.
Come on, buddy.
It's okay.
I am so screwed.
And now you're crippled for life.
Honey, watch the hair.
Go. Now. But be quiet.
Mom, wait!
Oh, my God!
- Mom...
- What happened?
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
What'd you do to my TV?
Look, Mom, I can explain.
We will talk about this later, all right?
- Now, I have to go.
- Are you kidding me?
No. You're not going anywhere.
- It's about my car. It's really important.
- About your car?
That you spend all day and night shut
in that garage, doing God-knows-what with?
Mom, I can't. I really can't right now.
Oh, no, you really can, Charlie.
You really can.
I have had it!
Your attitude, your always sulking around.
You brought home that piece of crap
without even asking me!
Everyone in this family
is trying to be happy,
and all you want to do
is make things harder.
You know, Mom,
just because you've moved on
and you're happy with your new life
doesn't mean I have!
You've found a replacement for my dad
and I haven't, okay, and I never will!
So I'm sorry if that makes things harder,
but in ten months from now
you won't even have to deal with me!
Charlie!
Hey, you okay?
Yeah.
I just feel like ever since my dad died,
I've become this drain on everyone,
and I hate it.
It's like everybody expects me
to act like nothing ever happened,
and it's impossible to do that.
About your dad, I'm really sorry.
Thanks.
You know, there's this quote that I like.
"The darkest nights
produce the brightest stars."
That's nice.
My mom got it from Weight Watchers.
Get out and move away from the vehicle.
Stay cool, Bee.
What's going on?
Hey!
- Come on!
- Stop it!
Let go of me!
- Weapons now! Take it down!
- Run!
No, don't run. Do not run!
She ran.
Please tell me they're on our side.
No more running.
No more hiding.
B-127, you're a traitor and a coward.
Tell us where Optimus Prime is hiding.
Bee, look out!
Why isn't he fighting back?
Why don't you fight?
Leave him alone! Please!
Again.
Hit it again!
Stop! Stop it!
Your daughter stole
government property, Mrs. Watson.
She's been having trouble adjusting,
but we had no idea it was this serious.
I...
Charlie. Honey.
I didn't steal anything,
and he doesn't belong to them.
- "He?"
- Ma'am.
I can assure you that it is an "it".
And "it" is a highly dangerous
war machine.
No, he isn't, okay, Mom?
He's not some "war machine."
I don't know what he is, but...
He's my friend.
Ma'am, your daughter's had
a traumatic experience today.
Maybe doesn't understand
everything she's seen.
She's disoriented.
No, I'm fine, Mom.
I'm completely fine, okay?
You have to believe me, please.
I didn't steal anything!
Stop! Just go to your room.
When I was going through puberty,
I stole things, too.
- Stole a box of Mallomars once.
- Yeah, we know.
Boom.
Caught you.
Mom's gonna love this.
Look, Otis, you need to go home and...
Mom!
No, Otis, stop it!
Why would you do that?
Let go of me!
You're touching my buttocks!
I will tell you a secret if you shut up.
Okay, so this is my room.
Just make yourself at home.
These are actually my sister's stuff.
She likes playing pranks,
like putting her stuff over here.
- Can I sit down?
- Yeah, yeah.
Residents of Brighton Falls
have been witness
to an unusual sight this evening.
Armed Forces pouring into town
as part of what we are told
is a routine military exercise
setting up camp
at our own McKinnon Air Base.
If Bumblebee's still alive,
that's where they're keeping him.
We have to go.
We have to try and save him.
Count me in. I'll take point.
- No, you won't.
- Come on.
No, Otis.
- But I can help. Master Larry says I...
- I need someone here.
I need someone reliable to make sure
that Mom and Ron don't know that I'm gone.
I'm someone reliable.
Hell, yeah, you are.
Good luck.
You, too.
Get over here.
Let's do this.
Tell us where Optimus Prime
and the rebels are hiding,
and we can end this war.
Talk!
Who is Optimus Prime?
This doesn't concern you, human Powell.
Last chance.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
It's a terrible idea,
but I've got to try it.
You can't get... Well, why don't you...
Stop, stop, wait...
- How'd you know the power was off?
- I didn't. Let's go.
Can I?
His memory cells are fried.
Finish him.
We will fight on. Regroup, rebuild,
and retake our home.
But we must find refuge first.
You will travel to Earth.
Once we've gathered the others,
we'll join you.
You must protect the planet.
If the Decepticons find it,
then our people are truly finished.
Stay safe, soldier.
I am coming.
Prime is coming here?
They're all coming here.
This is our chance to wipe out
the Autobot resistance for good.
We'll burn the whole planet to cinders.
We must get word to Cybertron immediately.
This is Burns.
Tell them to bring an army.
Burns, we made a terrible mistake.
Powell?
And thanks to our human allies,
I know just how to get the message home.
They're using our satellites.
They're calling an army.
They're gonna kill us all.
Thank you for your hospitality,
friend Powell.
He's all yours.
- No.
- Powell?
- You have to stop them!
- Powell!
Where's the Krazy Glue?
What, did she cut the wire to the TV?
Ron.
Charlie!
Nice! Reel-to-reel still works.
Where is your sister?
Charlie's fallen ill and must stay in
her bedroom for the rest of the evening.
She wishes not to be troubled.
Keep clear of her chambers.
What?
Charlie has fallen ill
and must stay in her bedroom
for the rest of the evening.
- She wishes not to...
- Otis!
Are you on drugs?
No, no. Mom, Mom, Mom.
- Please stop. Stop!
- Charlie!
- Mom, there is no reason to go...
- Where is she?
- Mom, stop!
- Quit it, Otis.
Where is she?
Otis?
I found a tower to transmit our message.
It's close.
B-127. I almost forgot.
I didn't.
No! Don't shoot!
No!
Bee!
Talk to me, Bee, talk to me.
I can fix this. I can fix this.
Charlie.
You got to wake up, Bee.
You got to wake up.
Please.
Charlie, we got to go.
- The gun.
- What?
The electric gun. Get it.
I can fix you.
Come on, Bee.
Come back to me.
Come on, give me the other one.
Bee, come on.
I can't lose you, too, Bee.
Please, Bee!
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Come on, Bee,
we've got to get you out of here.
Charlie, there's like
a million guys out there!
We got to move, now.
Come on, Bee, you've gotta get up.
Can you get up?
There's a door in my way.
They've got bombs!
- We got to go.
- Bee, come on.
Charlie!
You've gotta get up, come on.
- Three.
- Charlie!
- Two.
- Come on.
One.
- Charlie!
- Come on.
Memo?
Memo. Memo, wake up.
Easy.
Hold your fire!
Get the kid out of here.
Memo! Wake up, Memo!
- Come on, kid.
- Hey! No!
Bee!
Run!
- Let go of me!
- You need to get away from that thing.
- Take it down!
- No, stop!
- Stop it!
- Contain it and dismantle it!
Strip it down to parts!
Leave him alone! You don't understand.
Fight back, Bee!
- Bee!
- Kid, stop! It's a machine!
He's more human than you'll ever be!
That is enough!
Oh, shit.
Open fire!
Fall back! Take cover!
Bee!
Bee, stop!
You remember, don't you?
They're coming back.
Oh, God.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
We need to get out of here.
We've got to get you someplace safe.
Bee, stop. They will kill you!
If the Decepticons find Earth,
then our people are truly finished.
Okay. Then we fight.
Let's go, get in.
Go on. I'll buy you some time
with these guys.
You just kiss me?
On the cheek.
Still counts.
Halt!
Stop.
Well, that didn't work.
Move, move!
Faster, Bee, faster!
We should really look
into getting seatbelts.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
It's okay. She's gonna steal
the robot back, fight off the police,
kill two bigger robots,
and come right back home.
Shut up, Otis.
Folks, this just breaking.
There appears to be
a high-speed chase underway
just outside McKinnon Air Base.
Go right! Go right!
Closer. Closer.
You lose that car,
I will personally rip your face off.
- Oh, God!
- It's all under control.
- Charlie!
- Mom?
You pull that car over right this second.
This is very unsafe, what you're doing.
Mom, you got to get out of here, okay?
Mom...
You have to trust me, please!
Charlie!
- We got to help her, Ron!
- Hang on.
Oh, my God! Ron!
Get out of the way!
Oh, my gosh!
What are you doing?
I saw this on 'Miami Vice'.
God!
- I got it, I got it, I got it.
- Oh, my God!
Nice driving, Ron.
Is everyone okay?
Ron! We have a kid in the car!
I was trying to save the other kid!
What was I...
It was a lose-lose.
Otis? Otis, are you all right?
That was radical.
Preparing satellites
to transmit our message.
Okay. What's the plan?
This is the plan? I hate this plan.
Bee, I want to help.
I would hate anything
To happen to her
You're actually talking.
And you're listening to The Smiths.
Be careful.
Handle him! And finish the job this time!
Oh, shit!
How the hell am I gonna get up there?
There. The one on the tower.
You think these little chains can hold...
Okay.
Hold on!
What are you doing?
Come on.
No.
After I kill you,
I kill her.
Bee, no!
You missed.
You'll kill us both!
Bumblebee!
Oh, God.
You.
You need to get outta here.
What do you mean?
I mean my friends are coming.
And they're gonna be looking for him.
Thank you.
Hey, soldier!
I'm here. I made it.
What's going on?
World's already been saved, kid.
Cool.
Hey, can you call my mom?
This is it, Bee.
Let's go!
Bee, I can't go with you.
You've got people out there that need you.
And so do I.
I gotta let you go.
Thank you...
So much...
For giving me...
My voice.
Thank you for...
For making me feel like me again.
I'll never forget you.
Goodbye, Bumblebee.
No way.
You kidding me?
Are you telling me you could've been
a Camaro this whole time?
Oh, my God!
♪ Don't you forget about me
♪ Don't, don't, don't
♪ Will you stand above me
♪ Look my way
Never love me?
♪ Rain keeps falling, rain keeps falling
♪ Down, down, down
♪ Will you recognize me
♪ Call my name or walk on by...
Here you go, ma'am.
Baby.
Thank God you're all right.
Thanks for coming, Mom.
That was some driving, Ron.
Well, I've taken a few notes.
Otis.
They forced me to tell.
I'm glad they did.
I couldn't have done it without you guys.
Hey, Charlie.
I'll be right back, okay?
What happened to you today?
This?
You know, robot fights, high-speed chases,
international disasters.
The usual.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Yeah...
- Not quite there yet.
- Nope.
- Yep. Okay, okay.
- No. Yeah.
Old friend,
you kept this planet safe.
Because of you,
we have a future, B-127.
My name...
Is...
Bumblebee.
Let's see if we got something.
Oh, my God, yes!